

Lasse Lund-Egmose

Curriculum Vitae

Contact

☑ Ile@lledev.com

+45 23 90 21 19

LLEDev.com

in /Lasse-Lund-Egmose

Skills

- System development
- Project Planning/Management
- Object Oriented Design
- Algorithm Design
- Computational Mathematics
- Cryptography
- · Embedded Software
- OS Kernel Development
- C. Rust
- PHP, Laravel, React, SASS

Language skills (CEFR)

- English: C1
- Danish: C2
- German: ~B1/B2 (untested)

Great passion for computing

Ever since I, at age 13, experienced the magical feeling of creating something that is comprehensible by a computer, I've known, that tech is just right up my alley. Since then, I've worked hard to continuously broaden my skill set. Currently, I am studying towards a Civil Engineering (cand.polyt) degree in Software Technology at Technical University of Denmark (DTU), and furthermore, I have worked as a programmer for 3 years (2 of which part-time — while managing my studies).

Work experience

Backend Developer — Morningscore

Remote, 2019-2021

- Remote programming job regarding the Morningscore application, where I mostly worked on major projects, I had a great amount of responsibility, and I had to meet my deadlines — and did.
- I primarily dealt with the complex task of integrating towards other systems such as the payment gateway (Stripe) or the CRM system (HubSpot).

Backend Developer / Project Manager — Morning Train Odense C, 2018-2019

- Full-time programming and project management job at a web agency, where I made websites tailored to the need of our customers.
- I underwent a sales training program by "SalgsPiloterne".

1-week internship at University of Southern Denmark's IT infrastructure department Odense M, 2014

Education

Technical University of Denmark – DTU

Kongens Lyngby, 2019-now

- I am currently studying at DTU to become a Civil Engineer (cand.polyt) in Software Technology.
- I will finish my bachelor's degree in 2022 and my master's degree in 2024.
- Studied abroad at University of Leeds in fall 2021

Sct. Knuds Gymnasium (High school)

Odense M, 2015-2018

- · Focus on natural sciences.
- · Member of The Academy for Talented Youth (ATU).
- · Hired by Sct. Knuds Gymnasium to work as tutor in my final year.

☑ Ile@lledev.com

+45 23 90 21 19

LLEDev.com

in /Lasse-Lund-Egmose